<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Physx Noob</title><link>https://ashwinbalaji0811.github.io/firstTrial/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Physx Noob</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 17:33:46 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ashwinbalaji0811.github.io/firstTrial/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Flatland</title><link>https://ashwinbalaji0811.github.io/firstTrial/2021/09/flatland/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 17:33:46 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://ashwinbalaji0811.github.io/firstTrial/2021/09/flatland/</guid><description>Flatland book review Introduction: 💾 This is a satirical novel featuring a pentagon flatlander’s revelations and brain-twisting experience of space-land.The author takes us into a fictional world of flatland where all flat-shapes live. Squares, pentagons, hexagons, polygons and circles(very rare) detailing out the religion, politics, sex, race etc. The everyday lives, sense of perception of these members, their worldview etc. Here the author introduces the flat-lander pentagon to line-land inhabitants who are just lines of different lengths and can see only dots.</description></item><item><title>Pseudoscience</title><link>https://ashwinbalaji0811.github.io/firstTrial/2021/09/pseudoscience/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 10:33:46 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://ashwinbalaji0811.github.io/firstTrial/2021/09/pseudoscience/</guid><description>Pseudoscience Definition Pseudoscience consists of statements, beliefs, or practices that claim to be both scientific and factual but are incompatible with the scientific method.
Common Connotations of Pseudoscience All voodoo magic, ouija boards, superstitious explanations for natural observations, ghosts, god etc are considered Pseudoscience. Good that Scientists know that they can’t answer questions related to these. Why?
Science means (and it’s limitations) The Scientific Method Workflow There is an inherent flaw in the methods of Scientific Study.</description></item><item><title>My First Post</title><link>https://ashwinbalaji0811.github.io/firstTrial/2021/09/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 17:33:46 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://ashwinbalaji0811.github.io/firstTrial/2021/09/my-first-post/</guid><description>My First Post in Hugo Hugo is Awesome, you all should try it ASAP
list item 1 list item 3 list item 2 Subtitle here goes my glorious flabbergasting blabber</description></item></channel></rss>